My name is Dede Folie
and this is my daughter Phillipa Aboamah and Lawrence Aboamah
and this is my granddaughter called Aaliyah Aboamah.
My testimony goes like:
On the 12th of April 2016,, my granddaughter fell from the sixth floor in London
So after that, I rushed down the steps.
I had pressed the lift but the lift wasn't working so I started running down the steps.
She couldn't walk; she was totally paralyzed.
So the ambulance came and took her to the hospital.
She couldn't walk; she couldn't do anything.
I then went home. I was having the Anointed Water at home which I had gotten from The SCOAN.
So when I went home, I took the Anointed Water with me back to the hospital.
When I got to the hospital, I sprayed the water on her.
After I had sprayed the water, she started moving the first hand,
the second hand, her leg, and the second leg.
Before she moved her legs, I was holding the Holy Water.
I sprayed it on her. I said, "In the mighty name of Jesus, Aaliyah, be healed!
Raise up your leg!" because she wasn't doing anything, she couldn't raise her leg up.
She couldn't raise anything up. She was totally paralyzed so I just sprayed the water.
I said again, "In the mighty name of Jesus, Aaliyah, be healed! Raise your leg up!"
because it was left with one leg. She couldn't raise it up.
Immediately I sprinkled the Anointed Water, she raised her leg up.
Everybody was shouting and my daughter said, "Oh Mummy!"
After ministering the Morning Water, she began to walk. Is that correct?
Yes.
Ok. What happened today when you brought her to The SCOAN?
When I brought her to The SCOAN, she wasn't walking properly because of her spine.
She was always falling; she kept on falling. She couldn't walk properly.
So when we brought her now, by the grace of God, when Prophet T.B. Joshua came
and prayed for her, she started walking.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
She was having a body brace and a foot brace.
Ok. What happened today when the prophet laid his hand on her?
After the prophet prayed for her, without the brace, she is alright now.
She began to walk.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ for that!
Dede Folie & Family
Morning Water Testimony
This was the newspaper - they wrote about it in the newspaper.
It was written there: "It is a miracle she's walking again."
Dede Folie & Family
Morning Water Testimony
The fact that Aaliyah is able to walk today is remarkable.
She fell from this top floor window breaking her spine just six weeks ago.
Doctors feared she would never walk again.
I was just like in shock. I went running downstairs and whilst I was even running downstairs,
I was calling an ambulance. The woman wasn't getting the address.
She wasn't getting anything I was trying to say to her because I was so much in tears.
Still in the hospital but recovering fast, saved by a fortunate sequence of events.
When Aaliyah's mum got there, a witness persuaded her not to move the two-year-old,
protecting Aaliyah from further back injury.
At the time she was moaning, "Mum, mum!"
I replied, "Yes". Then the man told me, "You cant touch her because you will mess up the bones
in her body further because she has broken bones".
I think he knew that she had broken bones.
He was a blessing to actually be there because I would have carried her.
It's only when you are here that you get an idea of the scale of this fall.
We are on the ground floor. 50 feet higher is the fifth floor
and that's how far Aaliyah fell
It was extremely lucky that she didn't suffer much more serious injuries.
She could have indeed lost her life.
The speed with which she has recovered is very, very impressive.
1.2.3.4.5.6.7......
Where she fell from, the windows were open, there were satellite dishes.
I was just in shock. It was heartbreaking. It was traumatising.
And it was like, how did she not hit all the windows or the satellite dishes?
itv news
This was after you had administered the Morning Water on her.
After I had administered the Morning Water, she started walking.
She got out of the hospital bed and began to walk.
Yes, she began to walk.
It was amazing anyway because they were surprised.
All of them were asking me, "Oh how did you do it?"
because all of them had said that the baby wouldn't walk again.
After falling from such a height, she was supposed to be paralysed.
So the doctor told her that she was not going to walk again.
They even got her a wheelchair, everything for her,
and I told her, "I am serving a living God.
My granddaughter is going to walk again, in the name of Jesus!"
Then they said, "Oh". Another guy asked me, "Which church are you attending?"
I said, "I am attending The Synagogue Church Of All Nations".
You finally brought her to The Synagogue Church Of All Nations today...
Yes
...because her spinal cord was fractured and she was not steady in her movement.
Yes, she wasn't steady in her movement.
And what happened today when the prophet laid his hand on her?
When the prophet laid his hand on her, she started walking alright,
moving alright and everything was ok with her.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Ok. Let's hear briefly from the mother of the girl.
Tell us your name and where you come from.
My name is Phillipa Oboamah and I'm coming from London.
I just want to thank God for everything that He has done for me
because without Hi,m I dont think I would be here.
I think I would be going through stress or depression now if I hadn't turned to Him.
You heard it from her. She said that she is the mother of this little girl who had that accident
because she fell from the height of 60 feet.
Hello. I am Lawrence Boamah. This is my sister, my mum and my niece Aaliyah.
I would like to thank God for what He has done in my family's life and everything
because we never knew she would walk again.
She was actually having difficulty in walking
until my mum sprayed the Anointing Water on her.
It was just amazing because everyone in the hospital was shocked.
They were saying, "Ah, she wont walk again" and stuff like that.
My mum was praying all the time.
Everyone was praying with the Morning Water, praying to the God of T.B. Joshua.
I would like to thank God for what He has done in my family's life.
Ok. What happened to the life of your niece today when the prophet laid his hand on her?
After the prophet had laid his hand on my niece, she is walking alright now.
The brace is off now. As you can see, she is walking without the brace.
Ok. Now she doesnt need the brace anymore. What do you want to do with it?
I will throw it away.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
That is a clear proof that the little girl is completely free.
You heard it all. They said that they no longer want to use the body brace anymore
for this little girl because she is completely free.
Can you now go to the notice board and tell us the pictures we seeing there?
Explain the pictures.
Alright, This is a picture of when she fell and she was in an ambulance.
This one over here.
And this was when she was in intensive care.
This was when she wasn't even moving her leg - both of these pictures.
In all of these pictures she wasn't moving her leg
until my mum sprayed the Anointing Water. Then she started walking.
There are more pictures.
These are all pictures of when she was in intensive care.
So after ministering the Morning Water, she was actually the one who stood there.
She was walking. She wasn't even sitting on these things.
She wasn't sitting on these wheelchairs again. She was just walking around,
and that's when they gave her the brace.
When the prophet laid his hands on her, she started walking okay
and as you can see, she is walking okay.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ for that!
And finally, what word of advice do you have, Mama,
for what the Lord has done in the life of your granddaughter?
The advice I have for my fellow brothers and sisters:
Whenever you have a problem, seek the favour of God.
He is the only one who will help you.
Amen
I just want to say that everyone should watch their child wherever they go
and just give your faith to Christ.
Amen. We thank God Almighty for what He has done in the life of the little girl
as we can see her moving around. This is a clear proof that she could walk
after the touch from His able servant, Prophet T.B. Joshua
As you go and make the Word of God the standard for your life,
we pray your miracle will remain permanent, in Jesus' name
Amen.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
TT: Monica Asefa 18/06/18
RV: Mel Flowers 20/06/18